Washington Star 061 061
Stage
- Series 8: Leadership, 1853-1979
  - Theodore W. Noyes - Biographical, 1922-1939 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Theodore W. Noyes - Voting Rights, 1898-1929 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Theodore W. Noyes - Waterfalls, 1926-1929 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Owners List, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Partnership Agreement, 1867 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Profiles, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Alexander B. Shepherd - Portrait Reproduction, Undated (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Joseph B. Tate, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - John W. Thompson, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - William Wallach, Undated (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - James R. West, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Estate of Jessie C. Kauffmann, Undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Bequests, 1948-1949 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Cancelled Checks, 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Distribution of Jewelry, 1948 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Estate Tax Return, 1948 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records, 1910-1951 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Financial Records, 1910-1951 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Financial Records, 1910-1951 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Financial Records, 1910-1951 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Financial Records, 1910-1951 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Last Will and Testament, 1938 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Memorandum of Agreement - 1941, Undated (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Memorandum of Agreement - 1941, Undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Power of Attorney, 1946-1954 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Union Trust Co. Financial Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Union Trust Co. Financial Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Series 9: The Family Star, 1960-1971
  "The Family Star" was a newsletter written and published by and for the employees of the Star. It includes stories about employee awards, changes in benefits, and staff changes. The newsletters are arranged chronologically.
  - Untitled, 1960-1964 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1964-1971 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Series 10: BRI/Marketing Reports, 1966-1980
  BRI Marketing Reports were commissioned by the Star to track the spending habits of subscribers of the major DC papers based on race, gender, age, and economic status.
  - "Report on heaviness of use of products among homemakers and adult women in the average daily newspaper audiences of the three major newspapers in the Washington market", 1966 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - "Report on heaviness of use of products among homemakers and adult women in the exclusive and duplicated audiences of the Washington Star and Washington Post", 1966 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - "Report on heaviness of use of products among homemakers and adult women in the exclusive and duplicated audiences of the Washington Star and Washington Daily News", 1966 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Part 1 of 2: "Report on demographic characteristics of homemakers and adult women who are heavy, moderate, light, and non-users of specific products", 1966 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Part 2 of 2 "Report on demographic characteristics of homemakers and adult women who are heavy, moderate, light, and non-users of specific products", 1966 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - "Report on specific preferences of stores for purchase of specific products among total adult women in the average daily newspaper audiences of the three major newspapers in the Washington market", 1966 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - "Report on specific preferences of stores for purchase of specific products among total adult women in the exclusive and duplicated audiences of the Washington Star and Washington Post", 1966 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - "Report on specific preferences of stores for purchase of specific products among total adult women in the exclusive and duplicate audiences of the Washington Star and Washington Daily News", 1966 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - "Heaviness of use of products among total homemakers and adult women in Washington who are in the duplicated and unduplicated audiences of the three major Washington newspapers singly and in combination", 1966 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - "Report on heaviness of use of products among homemakers and adult women in the exclusive and duplicated audiences of the Washington Star and Washington Post, national female products", 1966 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - "Report on heaviness of use of products among homemakers and adult women in the exclusive and duplicated audiences of the Washington Star and Washington Daily News, national female products", 1966 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - "Report on heaviness of use of products among homemakers and adult women in the average daily newspaper audiences of the three major newspapers in the Washington market, national female products", 1966 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - "Readers per dollar delivered per 1,000 line ad by specific Washington newspapers among homemakers and adult women who are purchasers of specific products using local retail costs" (2 reports), 1966 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - "Report on demographic characteristics of total homemakers in the exclusive and duplicated audiences of the Washington Star and Washington Daily News", 1966 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - "Report on demographic characteristics of total homemakers in the exclusive and duplicated audiences of the Washington Star and Washington Post", 1966 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - "Report on demographic characteristics of homemakers in the average daily newspaper audiences of the three major newspapers in the Washington market", 1966 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - "Demographic characteristics among total Negro homemakers in the Washington market", 1966 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - "Report on demographic characteristics of total adult men with specific preferences of stores for purchase of specific products", 1966 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - "Report on demographic characteristics of total adult men in the average daily newspaper audiences of the three major newspapers in the Washington market", 1966 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - "The Three Sigma Syndicated Study of Major Market Newspaper Audiences-1980 Edition" Final Report (2 copies), Undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - "The Three Sigma Syndicated Study of Major Market Newspaper Audiences-1980 Edition" Summary Report (2 copies), Undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - "An Attitudinal and Behavioral Research Study Among Washington Area Residents", 1980 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Series 11: Libel Cases, 1888-1977
  This series contains correspondence, legal documents, and testimonies relating to various Libel Cases brought against the Star, chief among these being Ashford v. Star. The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Ashford vs. Star - Articles in Post and Herald, 1907 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Articles in Star, 1907-1908 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Ashford's Statement, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Case Law, 1902-1907 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Chronology, 1907 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Clippings, 1912 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Complaints and Case Law, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Dent's Statement, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Excerpts re: Building Inspector, 1908-1909 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Exhibit No. 2, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Headlines, 1907-1908 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Memorandum, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Memorandum, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Noyes Transcript and Testimony, 1912 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Perry's Opening Statement, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Pickford Apartment House Collapse, 1909 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Pleading, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Stevens Makes Charges, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Stevens' Resignation, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Stevens' Testimony, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Ashford vs. Star - Synopsis of Stevens' Charges, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1950-1960 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1910-1941 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Kilgour vs. Star, 1902 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Legal Issues, 1973-1977 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Libel Case Law and Notes, 1898-1908 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Look at this Every Day: Libelous Matter, Undated (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Marietta vs. Star, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Mooney vs. Star, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Ormsby vs. Star, 1909 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Star vs. IRS, 1932-1936 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Summary of Suits, 1870-1909 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Veidt vs. Star, 1888 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Webster vs. Star, 1908 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Whitaker vs. Star, 1939 (Box 80, Folder 35)
- Series 12: Buildings, 1902-1959
  This series contains clippings, correspondence, and other materials related to the various buildings that housed the Star. The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Historic Clippings, 1902-1939 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Historic Clippings, 1902-1939 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - South East Plant - Clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - South East Plant - Clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - South East Plant - Clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Parking Plaza, 1939-1940 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Series 13: History, 1851-1981
  The Star reached its centennial in 1952. Records used to write an historic edition of the newspaper for the centennial and other anniversaries are contained in this series. They include clippings, correspondence, chronologies, story copies, addresses, and copies of historic editions. The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - 25-50 Year Club, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Address: S. H. Kauffmann - 100th Anniversary, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Address: S. H. Kauffmann to Newcomen Members, Undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Address: B. M. McKelway at Welcome to Washington Dinner, 1951 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Allbritton Purchase of the Star, 1975-1978 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Allbritton Purchase of the Star, 1975-1978 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Allbritton Purchase of the Star, 1975-1978 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Allbritton Purchase of the Star, 1975-1978 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Allbritton Purchase of the Star, 1975-1978 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Article of Co-Partnership, 1867 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Article - Garfield Assassination, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Articles re: Washington Star, 1976-1979 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Bicentennial, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Building Directory, 1928 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Centennial, Undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Advertising, 1852-1952 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Advertising Ethics, 1895-1952 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Chronology, 1852-1925 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Chronology of News Events, 1852-1945 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Circulation, 1870-1952 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Congratulatory CorrespoUndatedence, 1952-1953 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Charters, 1890 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Dinner Seating List, 1952 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - DC Churches, 1852-1952 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - DC History, 1851-1950 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - DC History - Hospitals, 1871-1946 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Centennial, Undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - DC Public Building Projects, 1920-1952 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Editor Authority, 1945 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Feature Assignments, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Feature Assignments, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Journalism, 1864-1952 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Journalism, 1864-1952 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Linotype, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Mechanical Queries, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Music and Theatre in Washington, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Paper-Types Used by Star, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Parks, Undated (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Photo-Engraving, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Picture Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Population Statistics, 1850-1900 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Printing Presses, 1924-1952 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Promotion Department, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Public Health Statistics, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Reminiscences of the Star by R. M. Kauffmann, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Roto Section Outline, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Roto Section Outline, 1951-1952 (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Society Department, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - The Star's Family Tree, 1867-1952 (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Transportation in DC, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - Washington Gas Light Co., 1952 (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Women, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Chronology, 1949, Undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Chronology, 1949, Undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Chronology and Research, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Chronology and Research, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Chronology and Research, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Chronology and Research, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Chronology and Research, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Chronology and Research, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Circulation - Government Building Survey, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Circulation Statistics, 1926 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1882-1979 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1882-1979 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1882-1979 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1882-1979 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Clippings - 75th Anniversary, 1927 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Clippings - 90th Anniversary, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Clippings - Joel L. Allbritton, 1974-1977 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Clippings - Classified, 1881 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Clippings - Daily Critic challenge to the Star, 1880 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Clippings - New Building, 1899 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Clippings - New Building, 1899 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - CorrespoUndatedence, 1818-1972 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - CorrespoUndatedence - Jesse C. Suter, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - DC Bibliography, Undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Editorial Policy in War-Time Criticism, 1942 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Editorials re: Star, 1975-1977 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Employees, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Employees Anniversaries and Employee Lists, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Famous Star Extras, Undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Guided Tour, Undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Historic Front Pages, 1954-1965 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - History - Manuscript, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - History - Manuscript, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - History - Manuscript, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - History - Manuscript, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Issue Numbers - Chronology, 1947 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - JFK Assassination - "What We Shall Remember", 1963 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Jobs for the Jobless Series, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Know Your Paper - Manuscript, 1922-1923 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Media in Washington - Washington Post, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Narrative History, 1938-1951 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Narrative History, 1938-1951 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - New Building - article Huber News, 1958-1959 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - New Building - Report on Sites, 1954 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - News Clippings, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - News Clippings - Star Related, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - New Year's Address to Patrons of the Star - Broadside, 1858 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Press Release re: Star History, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Program - Luncheon Given by the Evening Star to the First Pan-American, Undated (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Congress of Journalists, 1926 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Prospectus of the Daily Evening Star, Undated (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Rotogravure Sections, 1919-1922 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Sale of Star to Time Life - Mastheads and Negatives, 1977-1979 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Seal - The Evening Star Newspaper Co., 1868 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Six-Month Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Star/Daily News Merger, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Star/Daily News Merger, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Star History, 1955-1977 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Star History, 1955-1977 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Star News Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Star News Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Stereotype, Undated (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Telegraph and Teletype, Undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 1877 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - "Uncle Sam" Wilson, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Washingtonian Article, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - 50th Anniversary, Undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - 100th Anniversary, Undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Final Edition Proof Roll, Undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Series 14: Awards and Certificates
  This series contains awards and certificates won by individuals, specific departments, and the Star.
  - Awards and Certificates, Undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Certificates, Undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Certificates, Undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Certificates, Undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Certificates, Undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Certificates, Undated (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Series 15: Scrapbooks/Guest Registers, 1894-1975
  The materials in this series are arranged chronologically. They include scrapbooks of clippings related to the Star and other historic events in Washington, DC.
  - (includes two folders of loose material), 1894-1905 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - (includes six folders of loose material), 1894-1905 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1906-1907 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - (includes one folder of loose material), 1906-1908 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1909-1911 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1911-1912 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1912-1912 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1912-1914 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1914-1915 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1915-1918 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1918-1922 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1922-1932 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1927-1929 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1932-1937 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1937-1940 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1940-1944 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1945-1949 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1949-1954 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1954-1961 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1961-1970 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1968-1971 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1970-1975 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - (two scrapbooks), 1972-1973 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Japan after War ca. 1946 (#1) and German Atrocities ca. 1945 (#4), 1946, 1945 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Alcoholic Clinics - 1946-1947 (#2) and Death of Frank Noyes - 1948 (#3), 1946-1947, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Louise Kauffman Simpson scrapbook (1930) and Guest Register (1959), 1930, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Series 16: Photographs, 1850-1981
  This series contains photographs and reprints of events at the Star, historic front pages, and individuals who worked at the Star. It also includes promotional images, photographic plates, and scenes around DC. The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Advertisements and Promotions, 1938-1979 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Capital Airlines, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Celebrities and Notable Figures, 1947-1981 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Dinner, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Dinner, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Dinner, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Centennial Dinner, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Dinner, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Dinner, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Centennial Dinner, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Centennial Dinner, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - DC Scenes, 1941-1968 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - DC Scenes, 1941-1968 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - DC Scenes - Downtown, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - DC Scenes - Downtown Renderings, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - DC Scenes - FBI Building, Undated (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - DC Scenes - FBI Building, Undated (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - DC Scenes - F Street NW, Undated (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - DC Scenes - F Street Demonstration Project, Undated (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - DC Scenes - HEW, Undated (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - DC Scenes - House Office Building, Undated (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - DC Scenes - Martin Luther King, Undated (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - DC Scenes - Unidentified, Undated (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - DC Scenes - Unidentified, Undated (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Fort Washington, 1950 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Fort Washington, 1950 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Historic Figures, Undated (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Historic Front Pages, 1854-1981 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Historic Front Pages, 1854-1981 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Historic Front Pages, 1854-1981 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Historic Front Pages, 1854-1981 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Historic Front Pages, 1854-1981 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Historic Images, 1850-1951 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Historic Images, 1850-1951 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Historic Images, 1850-1951 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Historic Images, 1850-1951 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Historic Images, 1850-1951 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Historic Images, 1860-1940 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Home Delivery, 1962-1976 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Leadership, Undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - National Symphony Orchestra-Star Commercial, 1979-1980 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - New Building, 1920-1921 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - New Building, 1920-1921 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - New Building, 1920-1921 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - New Building, 1920-1921 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Non-DC Scenes, 1948 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Owner Families - Adams Family, 1902-1940s (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Owner Families - Kauffman Family, 1902-1952 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Owner Families - Noyes Family, 1870s-1940s (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Owner Families - James R. Shepley (Chairman), 1981 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Photographers, 1967-1981 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Photo Albums, Undated (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Photo Albums, Undated (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Press Room, 1897-1973 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Press Room, 1897-1973 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Press Room, 1897-1973 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Press Room, 1897-1973 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Press Room, 1897-1973 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Press Room, 1897-1973 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Staff (see also Series XXII: Negatives), 1950-1970 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Staff (see also Series XXII: Negatives), 1950-1970 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Staff (see also Series XXII: Negatives), 1950-1970 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Staff (see also Series XXII: Negatives), 1950-1970 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Staff, 1963-1970 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Staff, 1963-1970 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Staff, 1963-1970 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Staff, 1963-1970 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Staff, 1963-1970 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Staff, 1963-1970 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Composing Room, Undated (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Staff, 1894 (Box 128, Folder 1)